transd.info 2013-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Trans-D Tropin®

We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. 

**Why did you receive an email from us?**  
If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings. 

**How we protect your privacy**  
We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. 

**Sharing and Usage**  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. 

We use the information we collect about you to improve the content of our website, process orders and order confirmations, respond to your inquiries, and to provide you with a more personalized shopping experience. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TransD.com and we reserve the right to share information collected hereunder with our own affiliates. 

We may store the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail and add you to our mailing list when you sign up to receive special promotions and updates. By electing to receive e-mails from us, we are able to send you exclusive information and special offers, which you may otherwise not learn about. Follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of these e-mails to cease receiving them. Requesting removal will not prevent you from receiving e-mail communications relating to any online order you place with us. 

TransD.com does not currently sell, trade or rent your personal information, including e-mail addresses, to others; however, we do reserve the right to disclose personal information as obligated by law, in response to duly authorized legal process, governmental requests and as necessary to protect the rights and interests of TransD.com. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**USE OF THIRD PARTIES:**  
We use third parties to help us provide services to you including such things as fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, maintaining our database, administering e-mails, and administering drawings or contests, and to provide aggregate, comparative information on the performance of our site to us and a select group. Information will be shared with these third parties only to the extent necessary to provide these services. 

TransD.com may use certain companies that enable you to establish a membership to participate in digital wallets, payment services or rewards programs. If you elect to do so, we would only disclose to such companies the information necessary to make their programs work and support your membership with them. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the companies sponsoring these membership programs and we suggest you review the individual privacy policies of each company with whom you establish a membership. 

**How can you stop receiving email from us?**  
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email. 

If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [**info@TransD.com**](mailto:info@transD.com) for review.
